{
  "openingRemarks": "Do not bother to simplify the result<br>E.g. can enter \\(\\dfrac{250}{100}\\) as \\(2\\frac{50}{100}\\) instead of \\(2\\frac{1}{2}\\)<p>Also enter \"n/a\" for any result which is not defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Express \\(20 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(53 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(15 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(17 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(8 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(17 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(29 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(11 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(9 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(13 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(8 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(39 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(6 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(6 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(13 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(6 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(27 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(26 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(44 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(23 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(7 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(34 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(35 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(35 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(47 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(7 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(35 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(39 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(5 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(26 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(9 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(34 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(7 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(15 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(31 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(31 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(20 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(29 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(49 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(19 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "9 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(41 \\div 7\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 6/7"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(23 \\div 6\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 5/6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(8 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(39 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "7 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(44 \\div 9\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 8/9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(23 \\div 8\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 7/8"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(17 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "8 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(27 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "6 3/4"
    }
  ]
}
